https://orientaljadejewelry.com/privacy-and-security/

Skip to content
HomeABOUT USABOUT JADEABOUT JADEJade SymbolsA Brief History of JadePRODUCTSJade BanglesJade BraceletsJade NecklacesJade EarringsJade PendantsJADE FIGURESJade RingsONE OF A KIND, RARE AND ESTATE ITEMSBlogCONTACT
Menu HomeABOUT USABOUT JADEABOUT JADEJade SymbolsA Brief History of JadePRODUCTSJade BanglesJade BraceletsJade NecklacesJade EarringsJade PendantsJADE FIGURESJade RingsONE OF A KIND, RARE AND ESTATE ITEMSBlogCONTACT
$0.00
Cart
609-704-1188
Facebook
Search
HomeABOUT USABOUT JADEABOUT JADEJade SymbolsA Brief History of JadePRODUCTSJade BanglesJade BraceletsJade NecklacesJade EarringsJade PendantsJADE FIGURESJade RingsONE OF A KIND, RARE AND ESTATE ITEMSBlogCONTACT
Menu HomeABOUT USABOUT JADEABOUT JADEJade SymbolsA Brief History of JadePRODUCTSJade BanglesJade BraceletsJade NecklacesJade EarringsJade PendantsJADE FIGURESJade RingsONE OF A KIND, RARE AND ESTATE ITEMSBlogCONTACT
Our Online Transaction SecurityThe use of the latest cutting edge technology ensures that your experience with us will be safe and secure. We encrypt your personal information including your name, address, and credit card number when you submit order on our site, using the latest secure socket layer (SSL) security software. This guarantees that all the information you typed into our secure checkout system will be data encrypted from the moment you process your order.We constantly update our security system software to exceed the latest encryption standards so that all your sensitive personal information is perfectly secure on our site.SO, Feel Safe, Secure, and Shop with confidenceOur Privacy PolicyYour privacy is our highest priority, and our policy on customer privacy has always been NEVER to share our valued customer’s personal information with anyone (since 1985)!!!We have always stood by this and always will. Terms & ConditionsThese terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Oriental Jade Jewelry’s Website.Oriental Jade JewelryBy accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions in full. Do not continue to use Oriental Jade Jewelry’s websiteif you do not accept all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and any or all Agreements: “Client”, “You” and “Your” refers to you, the person accessing this website and accepting the Company’s terms and conditions. “The Company”, “Ourselves”, “We”, “Our” and “Us”, refers to our Company. “Party”, “Parties”, or “Us”, refers to both the Client and ourselves, or either the Clientor ourselves. All terms refer to the offer, acceptance and consideration of payment necessary to undertake the process of our assistance to the Client in the most appropriate manner, whether by formal meetings of a fixed duration, or any other means, for the express purpose of meeting the Client’s needs in respect of provision of the Company’s stated services/products, in accordance with and subject to, prevailing law of . Any use of the above terminology or other words in the singular, plural, capitalisation and/or he/she or they, are taken as interchangeable and therefore as referring to same.CookiesWe employ the use of cookies. By using Oriental Jade Jewelry’s website you consent to the use of cookiesin accordance with Oriental Jade Jewelry’s privacy policy.Most of the modern day interactive web sites use cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate / advertising partners may also use cookies.LicenseUnless otherwise stated, Oriental Jade Jewelry and/or it’s licensors own the intellectual property rights forall material on Oriental Jade Jewelry. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may view and/or printpages from https://orientaljadejewelry.com/ for your own personal use subject to restrictions set in these terms and conditions.You must not:Republish material from https://orientaljadejewelry.com/Sell, rent or sub-license material from https://orientaljadejewelry.com/Reproduce, duplicate or copy material from https://orientaljadejewelry.com/Redistribute content from Oriental Jade Jewelry (unless content is specifically made for redistribution).Hyperlinking to our ContentThe following organizations may link to our Web site without prior written approval:Government agencies;Search engines;News organizations;Online directory distributors when they list us in the directory may link to our Web site in the samemanner as they hyperlink to the Web sites of other listed businesses; andSystemwide Accredited Businesses except soliciting non-profit organizations, charity shopping malls,and charity fundraising groups which may not hyperlink to our Web site.These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so longas the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement orapproval of the linking party and its products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linkingparty’s site.We may consider and approve in our sole discretion other link requests from the following types of organizations:commonly-known consumer and/or business information sources such as Chambers of Commerce, AmericanAutomobile Association, AARP and Consumers Union;dot.com community sites;associations or other groups representing charities, including charity giving sites,online directory distributors;internet portals;accounting, law and consulting firms whose primary clients are businesses; andeducational institutions and trade associations.We will approve link requests from these organizations if we determine that: (a) the link would not reflect unfavorably on us or our accredited businesses (for example, trade associations or other organizations representing inherently suspect types of business, such as work-at-home opportunities, shall not be allowed to link); (b)the organization does not have an unsatisfactory record with us; (c) the benefit to us fromthe visibility associated with the hyperlink outweighs the absence of link is in the context of general resource information or is otherwise consistent with editorial content in a newsletter or similar product furthering the mission of the organization.These organizations may link to our home page, to publications or to other Web site information so long as the link: (a) is not in any way misleading; (b) does not falsely imply sponsorship, endorsement or approval of the linking party and it products or services; and (c) fits within the context of the linking party’s site.If you are among the organizations listed in paragraph 2 above and are interested in linking to our website, you must notify us by sending an e-mail to jac16@verizon.net. Please include your name, your organization name, contact information (such as a phone number and/or e-mail address) as well as the URL of your site, a list of any URLs from which you intend to link to our Web site, and a list of the URL(s) on our site to which you would like to link. Allow 2-3 weeks for a response.Approved organizations may hyperlink to our Web site as follows:By use of our corporate name; orBy use of the uniform resource locator (Web address) being linked to; orBy use of any other description of our Web site or material being linked to that makes sense within thecontext and format of content on the linking party’s site.No use of Oriental Jade Jewelry’s logo or other artwork will be allowed for linking absent a trademark licenseagreement.IframesWithout prior approval and express written permission, you may not create frames around our Web pages oruse other techniques that alter in any way the visual presentation or appearance of our Web site.Reservation of RightsWe reserve the right at any time and in its sole discretion to request that you remove all links or any particular link to our Web site. You agree to immediately remove all links to our Web site upon such request. We also reserve the right to amend these terms and conditions and its linking policy at any time. By continuing to link to our Web site, you agree to be bound to and abide by these linking terms and conditions.Removal of links from our websiteIf you find any link on our Web site or any linked web site objectionable for any reason, you may contact us about this. We will consider requests to remove links but will have no obligation to do so or to respond directly to you.Whilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on the website is kept up to date.Content LiabilityWe shall have no responsibility or liability for any content appearing on your Web site. You agree to indemnify and defend us against all claims arising out of or based upon your Website. No link(s) may appear on any page on your Web site or within any context containing content or materials that may be interpreted as libelous, obscene or criminal, or which infringes, otherwise violates, or advocates the infringement or other violation of, any third party rights.DisclaimerTo the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website (including, without limitation, any warranties implied by law in respect of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and/or the use of reasonable care and skill). Nothing in this disclaimer will:limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence;limit or exclude our or your liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;limit any of our or your liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; orexclude any of our or your liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.The limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section and elsewhere in this disclaimer: (a) are subject to the preceding paragraph; and (b) govern all liabilities arising under the disclaimer or in relation to the subject matter of this disclaimer, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty.To the extent that the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature.Credit & Contact InformationThis Terms and conditions page was created at termsandconditionstemplate.com generator. If you have any queries regarding any of our terms, please contact us.
OUR PRODUCTS
Jade Bangles
Jade Bracelets
Jade Pendants
Jade Earrings
Jade Figures
Jade Rings
Jade One of a kind
Jade Necklaces TESTIMONIALS I received my jade pendant today and wanted to email your company to say that I am wearing it now and may never take it off. I just love it. Thanks for making it avalible on the internet at that great price.Thanks Mary J., Harford, Mass Beautiful jade merchandise, thanks. Will buy again Thanks Marilynn T., La Mirada, CA Great jade, the color and design. Everything is better than computer picture. Thanks for making me a happy customer.Thanks Nancy K., Hoquiam, WA Great earrings, color nicer than picture. Great bargain price also.Thanks L. J., Burge, France I received my bracelet, very good lavender color, as Stated on the website page " the jade colors are even Better than the pictures. Great service transaction. Thanks Carole Mungai Olympia,Wa. Carole M., Olympia, WA Very nice pendant, nicer than pictured. I am very satisfied ThanksTamara F., South Houston, TX I simply love the necklack. Your description and picture were right on target. I will make your website my No 1 site for jade jewelry. (I’m a jade lover) ThanksJanice S., Cherry Hill, N.J. Lovely jade earrings. Fast turnaround. Great website very informative. I will be back again. ThanksLinda M., Ontario, Canada Excellent jade products and transaction every step of the way. A1 service. Keep up the great work ThanksS. Johnson N., United Kingdom Thanks for delivering what you actually show in your website. I have Bought from other websites in the past and was only half satisfied with my purchase. I took another chance and bought from you because I loved the product shown and you have a 100% Guarantee customer Satisfaction. When it arrived I was more than happy to see that my necklace was the same as I saw in my computer screen. I am a very satisfied and happy customer.Linda R., San Diego, CA I just received the jade pendant, it’s beautiful. I took it it my jeweler that sells jade and he told me that the quality was excellent and I Got a great deal. I am thrilled with my purchase and just wanted to let you know.Kaipo, Honolulu, HI Beautiful merchandise, fast service as the last time. I rate your site and products A+ ThanksPhillis J., Austin, TX
Previous
NextPAGES
Home
About Us
About Jade
Our Policy
Blog
Contact
Privacy Policy
Testimonials
Buy authentic Jade jewelry at discount prices here at Orientaljadejewelry.com.Copyright© 1997-2020 Oriental Jade Jewelry, All Rights ReservedWebmaster – Sagapixel
OUR PRODUCTS
Jade Bangles
Jade Bracelets
Jade Pendants
Jade Earrings
Jade Figures
Jade Rings
Jade One of a kind
Testimonials
Privacy Policy TESTIMONIALS I received my jade pendant today and wanted to email your company to say that I am wearing it now and may never take it off. I just love it. Thanks for making it avalible on the internet at that great price.Thanks Mary J., Harford, Mass Beautiful jade merchandise, thanks. Will buy again Thanks Marilynn T., La Mirada, CA Great jade, the color and design. Everything is better than computer picture. Thanks for making me a happy customer.Thanks Nancy K., Hoquiam, WA Great earrings, color nicer than picture. Great bargain price also.Thanks L. J., Burge, France I received my bracelet, very good lavender color, as Stated on the website page " the jade colors are even Better than the pictures. Great service transaction. Thanks Carole Mungai Olympia,Wa. Carole M., Olympia, WA
Previous
Next
Buy authentic Jade jewelry at discount prices here at Orientaljadejewelry.com.Copyright© 1997-2020 Oriental Jade Jewelry, All Rights ReservedWebmaster – Sagapixel
